I can't believe
you've fallen for this again.
You crazy?
We've got Lindor. Soto.
and Baschel leading off.
Yeah. it's like
a video game lineup.
Exactly.
So what's the problem?
The problem is that
the front of their jersey
still says Mets.
The National League
Championship Series.
and honestly...
Something wrong?
No.
Maybe.
Probably late to work.
Look out!
Dispatch. alpha tango six!
We are under attack!
I repeat. we are under attack!
Dispatch. do you read?
Come in!
My phone ain't working
either. man.
They must be
jamming our signal.
Hold on.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
If this truck stops.
we're sitting ducks.
We've got three minutes.
Let's move.
Open up.
Open up. or I'll blow it.
Good boy.
Shoot it down!
- You're leaking.
- Oh. it's just a scratch.
You guys are
making a mistake.
We can't open the cargo bay.
Now. don't worry.
We brought our own key.
I have a feeling it's
gonna be one of those days.
I should have called in sick.
This is a total mess.
A total and complete
inside-out mess.
Things weren't like this
when we signed up. Maggie.
The whole world feels like
it's coming apart at the seams.
Well. at least
we have each other.
Isobel.
Thank you for getting here
so quickly.
- Yeah. of course.
- This one's a red ball.
What happened?
At 7:15 a.m..
an armored transport
departed the Kingsdale
Institute for Virology.
It's a federally funded
BSL 3 lab.
Yeah. they study
dangerous pathogens.
Where were they headed?
An off-site government
storage facility.
But four masked thieves
hit the truck
before it ever got there.
In broad daylight
on a parkway.
Yeah. they cut open
the back door
and took high-risk
biohazard samples.
all in the matter
of three minutes.
High-risk?
What did they steal.
anthrax or SARS?
Well. I'm afraid
that information
is above your pay grade.
Mine too. apparently.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I do not like
doing my job blindfolded.
but the JOC is in communication
with the CDC.
We've got to figure out
who hit this truck and fast.
Understood.
They bricked the engine
with something heavy.
By the size of the crater.
it's looking like a 50-cal.
So not just highly trained.
they're highly resourced.
What are the chances
this was an inside job?
It's too soon to say.
Witnesses saw the crew
abduct the driver
and the guard at gunpoint.
If the rip was successful.
why kidnap the employees?
Covering their tracks?
Well. looks like
they left one.
All right. folks. come on in.
Listen up.
45 minutes ago.
a highly skilled team
hit an armored transport
coming from Kingsdale
Institute of Virology.
The driver. Teddy Navado.
and a guard. Bradley McCoy.
were both abducted.
along with one container
of unidentified
pathogen samples.
Yeah. but if
we don't have clearance
to know what they took.
how are we supposed to know...
Yes. we need to operate as if
we are dealing with the worst.
But. you know. feel free
to hope for the best.
All right. where are we?
Any leads on the forerunner
our crew was using?
Plates are fake.
- Put out a BOLO just in case.
- Great. yeah.
Send it wide. What else?
Yeah. I ran the DNA
from that blood smear
Maggie found through CODIS.
It was a dead end.
OK. please tell me there's
a subordinating conjunction
coming.
Until I cross-reference it
with the DOD's database
for identifying remains.
you know. just in case.
Meet Devon Reinhardt.
OK. eyes up!
He's a former Army Ranger.
two tours in the Middle East.
discharged three years ago.
No work history since.
Oh. OK.
Special ops guys aren't known
to sit on their hands.
No work in three years?
That's what it says
officially.
Well. officially.
I'm not buying it.
Officially.
I wouldn't even rent it.
This guy's been working
in the shadows.
Yeah. working hard
to steal something
we don't even have clearance
to get read in on.
Something's not adding up.
Well. let's not fight.
You have an LKA?
Yeah. Sunset Park.
Lives with a Tanya Mills.
All right.
let's go meet Tanya.
Stay frosty.
We don't know what
we're walking into here.
Tanya Mills.
FBI.
Oh. no. no. I wouldn't do that.
Can you set the bag down
for me. please?
Let's sweep the house.
Devon Reinhardt... are we gonna
find him in there?
Federal agents!
Devon hasn't been here
in weeks.
OK.
You're just. what.
going on a grocery run. is it?
Look. Tanya.
we don't have time for lies.
Your boyfriend just robbed
an armed transport
carrying deadly
pathogen samples
and kidnapped the driver
and the guard.
No. no way.
There's... he would never.
I got his blood at the scene.
So tell me where he is. Tanya.
That's... Devon disappears
for months at a time.
He never tells me
where he goes.
All I know is that
when he's back.
the fridge is full
and the bills are paid.
That's funny.
because his file says that
he hasn't worked
in three years.
I don't think
you're understanding
the seriousness
of the situation. OK?
People could die. all right?
So do you want to be
an accessory to that?
No. no. no. no.
Look. Devon called
this morning.
He said to go into the shed
and grab a bag.
Said that I'd understand
once I looked inside.
This bag?
Everything you'd need
to survive a bio attack.
You clearly know something.
So if you can't tell us
where he is.
then tell us who he's with.
When Devon called
this morning.
I heard a voice
in the background.
It had to be Charlie.
Who's Charlie?
Charlotte "Charlie" Martinez. 35.
She's an ex-MARSOC Raider.
According to Tanya.
she and Devon are tight.
Owns the bar
Devon made his call
from inside this morning.
OK. so a Special Ops Marine
and an Army Ranger
steal a pathogen.
They do it for money
or ideology?
Ask them yourself
when you get them into custody.
Let's move in... quietly.
FBI! Hands up!
Drop your weapons!
Everyone. take it easy.
Devon Reinhardt.
we know you and your guys
hit up that armored truck
this morning.
Where's the pathogen?
We're asking
the same question.
I told you already.
we don't have it.
Whatever's going on here.
it ends now.
Not even close.
Oh. you all are way out
over your skis.
This is a sanctioned op.
Sanctioned by who?
By me.
Everything we've done today.
we did on behalf
of the U.S. government.
So lower your weapons.
Anna Vorpe.
Isobel. can I speak with you
for a second first?
No. we're late.
and Anna Vorpe is
briefing us on her op.
Look. apparently.
whatever was on that truck
is still out there.
Isobel.
she had two U.S. citizens
hooked up to car batteries.
We can't just
look the other way.
Listen. when she sent Oslo
into 26 Fed.
I tried to expose her.
The Secretary of Defense
contacted me personally.
She is protected.
Only a silver bullet
could take her out.
If this doesn't qualify.
what does?
That is not a riddle
we're gonna solve today.
Come on.
Kingsdale isn't a BSL 3 lab.
It is a top-secret
BSL 4 gain-of-function
research facility.
Where. what.
scientists study
the most dangerous pathogens
on the planet?
Close.
They design them.
modify them.
make doomsday weapons
that can fit in your pocket.
Kingsdale houses
exotic infectious agents
with high fatality rates
and no known treatments.
So something real bad
got out?
NSA picked up chatter
about an imminent bio attack
in New York City using
a deadly novel pathogen
studied only at Kingsdale.
Turns out. that pathogen
was scheduled for transport
this morning
to a secure facility.
Why not just cancel
the transport.
keep it back at Kingsdale?
The truck was
already on the road
by the time we got the intel.
Our primary theory
was that terrorists
were gonna attempt to steal it
from its destination.
We had to act fast.
So you hit the truck en route
to take the pathogen
off the board.
Yeah. but the pathogen
wasn't in the truck.
The original vials had
been tampered with.
So you thought that
the driver and the guard
had something to do with it?
Yeah.
So you kidnap
and torture them for intel?
Enhanced interrogation.
And how'd that
work out for you?
They were clean. turns out.
Enough.
We have to assume
the hostile actors
are in possession
of a deadly bioweapon
that could decimate the city.
We're on it.
No.
The FBI will assist Anna's team
in recovery of the pathogen.
She'll run point.
No. not...
not until she tells us
exactly what the hell it is
we're dealing with.
All right. folks. listen up.
We finally know what
we're hunting. and it is. uh...
- Bad.
- Yes. that.
It's a pathogen called EMA.
which is short
for Emuro Arenaviridae.
Tell us about it.
- So. guys.
this is one of the most
transmittable RNA viruses
known to epidemiologists.
It originates
from rodent reservoirs.
and it's airborne.
According to records
that Anna Vorpe shared.
this is a synthesized strain
that causes hemorrhagic fever.
delirium. organ failure.
all within 36 hours
of exposure.
The fatality rate is 98%.
Right. and there's
no known treatment.
So if this thing were
to get out into the wild.
it would be catastrophic.
And that is being generous.
This is NIH's simulation
of an EMA outbreak
in New York City
after 12 hours.
24. 36.
That would wipe out
half the city.
Yeah. we're not gonna
let that happen.
All right. so how do we find
this pathogen?
Well. I think it's safe
to assume the samples
never made it onto
that transport van. right?
So they must have been taken
directly from the lab.
Who was the lead virologist
at Kingsdale?
These aren't flu vaccines.
When we transport
deadly pathogens.
there are protocols
on top of protocols.
The vials that we found
on the armored truck
labeled EMA
had been tampered with. OK?
They turned out to be
some kind of mixture
of sodium hydrochloride.
- That's household bleach.
OK. that tells me that
the vials from your lab
never made it onto the truck
in the first place.
You don't understand.
A designated
biosafety officer oversees
sample shipments
from start to finish.
Isn't that
biosafety officer you?
Yes. I packaged the samples
in a hermetically
sealed container.
and I prepped them
for relocation.
But they were all there
when I left the lab last night.
Unless...
Unless what?
Someone must have
swapped the EMA out
with sodium hypochlorite
before I packed them up.
But that would be insane.
So you're saying that anybody
could just tamper
with your samples?
No. of course not.
Specimen fridge only opens
with a badge.
So if it wasn't you
that opened up the fridge
and swapped out the samples.
who was it?
Meet Dr. Abadi's
lab assistant. Eloise Karcher.
She arrived at Kingsdale
yesterday morning.
and you'll see
she's not carrying anything.
Now. this is her leaving
at 10:17 p.m.
Notice anything different?
Yeah. she's got luggage.
All right. so it looks like
our inside man is a woman.
And she walked
those pathogen samples
right out the front door
last night.
So where is she now?
Have we been able to track her
since then?
Negative.
Phone's been offline for hours.
OK. NYPD and Port Authority.
I want her face plastered
all over the city.
Meantime. what do we know
about Dr. Karcher?
Anything we can use
to track her?
She's a postdoctoral fellow
at Kingsdale.
Been working there two years.
OK. so is she a foreign plant
or a part of
a domestic terror group?
She grew up in Rhinebeck.
no political affiliation.
no money problems.
never even left the country.
It seems like her whole life
has been dedicated
to studying viruses.
It doesn't make any sense.
A passionate virologist
like her
would want safe preservation
of EMA.
Passionate is one thing.
Angry is another.
Looks like
Eloise was very vocal online
about the recent cuts
to government funding.
"This is beyond shameful.
"Cutting funding
to labs like Kingsdale
will be death to us all."
Eloise was upset.
She was looking for ways
to be heard.
Yeah. but would she really
release a deadly pathogen
into the city?
Look at this commenter
right here. Dr. Jason Kisling.
Who is he?
Looks like
they know each other?
Yeah. Eloise often refers
to his research.
Yeah. Dr. Jason Kisling
is a renowned virologist
who's working out of Porton
Down in Wiltshire. England.
OK. so look at this.
He posted that he's gonna
DM her a bold opportunity.
Can we get in her DMs?
Uh. yeah.
Here we go.
OK. looks like
Dr. Kisling started
with commiserating
about her lost funds.
They talk about her lab.
Whoa. he gets her
to confide that
the project she's working on
at Kingsdale is EMA.
Oh. that sounds
like elicitation.
Yeah.
He says his lab has been
studying EMA for years.
but his country doesn't
have access to the pathogen.
OK. so he's buttering her up.
trying to get her to share
her samples. right?
Well. what does he
have to offer?
Lab space? Funding?
Can't tell you.
Eloise moved the conversation
to a burner phone...
said it would be safer.
Ping that phone
and send a team.
Eloise Karcher's phone
pinged to this terminal.
We need 50 sets of eyeballs
to scan this place.
Yeah. let's split up.
Jubal. we could use
some eyes in the sky.
Yep. Port Authority
is already on it.
Gold star
for whoever finds her.
OA. at the cafe.
I see her.
Jubal. we have
a possible hit on Eloise.
Moving in now.
FBI.
Let go of your bag.
and put your hands up.
Turn around slowly.
It's not her.
I repeat. not her.
Sorry.
Where is she?
Come on.
OK. that... that's her. right?
Yeah. that's her.
She's in the lounge.
Scola and Eva.
try to intercept her.
but approach with caution.
If that virus gets out...
Do not finish that sentence.
Wait a sec.
We've got two male suspects
approaching Eloise.
Yeah. who are these guys?
Hey. Kelly. you want
to run these guys?
Yeah. these guys are
about 40 years too young
to be Dr. Kisling.
So either he's using cutouts...
Or she got catfished.
Yeah. we're trying
to ID him back here.
but you guys just stay close.
All right.
We got eyes on the pathogen.
Two coolers.
Yeah. it's a handoff.
Yeah. whoever they are.
they are the ones
that set this in motion.
Let's wait until
the bioweapon changes hands
before you move in... copy?
Copy.
Hold on. she's getting spooked.
Can you hear
what they're saying?
Negative.
Look. we gotta move in.
She's bailing.
- No. no. no.
- Shots fired! Shots fired!
Do not lose that virus!
All right. where'd they go?
Where'd they go?
Top right.
Yep.
All right. guys. they're
running to short-term parking
through the North Hallway.
Look out.
Ah!
Hey!
Scola!
All right. how many
are we dealing with here?
Where'd they go?
Where the hell did they go?
I have no idea!
Jubal. we need
to cordon off the terminal.
They got away.
What about the bioweapon?
Gone.
The two assailants. posing
as virologists from the UK.
just shot and killed
Eloise Karcher
in the Kanto Airlines
terminal at JFK
and made off
with the EMA samples.
Somebody has got to give me
a bead on these guys
before they release
holy hell on all of us.
They can't have gotten too far.
Yeah. I got them.
They fled west towards
Federal Circle.
accessing this stairwell for
the short-term parking garage.
OK. great.
Where'd they go from there?
They completely
fell off the radar.
They must have jumped
into a getaway car.
But 15 vehicles left this lot
over the last three minutes.
It could be any one of them.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
OK. I need Port Authority
to stop and search
each one of these 15 vehicles.
This is officially a manhunt.
- It's gonna be tough.
I'm on with them.
It's rush hour.
They're trying
to seal the exits.
Have you mentioned
the bioweapon?
Hey. Jubal.
we just got a facial rec hit
off the CCTV footage.
Your day's about to get worse.
What?
All right.
so this is Jaco Coetzee
and this is Darren Blieden.
both members
of a violent terrorist cell
from South Africa
known as Vyrestrat.
a racial
essentialist organization
known for attacks in
Brazil. Angola. and the UK.
Do we know what they want
with the bioweapon?
Well. that's anyone's guess.
But if past is prologue.
Interpol says
they've been known to target
city parks. public spaces.
deploying bombs.
opening fire
on unsuspecting crowds.
Well. you're awfully quiet.
You knew about Vyrestrat.
No. our chatter didn't name
the group. but I know them.
They're as bad as they come.
Jaco's their leader.
He's organized.
determined. ruthless.
Use your imagination.
Yeah. now he and his pals
got their hands on one
of the deadliest pathogens
known to man.
We have to prepare
for an imminent bio attack.
Alert all
three-letter agencies.
And let's put a BOLO out
for Jaco and Darren.
Hold on.
I told you.
this case is classified.
I appreciate your help today.
but we've got it from here.
You cannot tie our hands with
American lives on the line.
Ma'am. we just got a hit
on Jaco Coetzee
on 7th and 52nd.
Heading to Central Park?
No. he's walking south. actually.
Times Square.
Your team cannot possibly
cover all of that ground.
Fine.
but we're running point.
me and my team.
We still have a job to finish.
I don't like
playing second fiddle
to a bunch of cowboys.
The way I look at it.
we're here to make sure
that the job gets done
the right way.
Maggie. there he is.
Where's he going?
All teams. we have
a visual on Coetzee.
He's at the corner
of 47th and 7th.
He has the cooler.
We need to assume that
the bioweapon is inside.
We're coming your way up.
We'll take him down then.
- Negative.
There are too many
civilians in the area.
We need to isolate him
before we apprehend him.
Devon. do you copy?
We got this.
Damn it.
Hey. Scola. Eva.
He's running east
on 48th Street.
FBI!
Out of the way!
No one move.
or I'm gonna shoot!
Jaco Coetzee.
get off the bus
and drop the bag.
Show me your hands!
I don't have eyes on him.
Devon. what are you doing?
You might hit the bioweapon.
Got a clean shot.
You're target-locked.
Dial it back.
No. no. no. no. no.
Oh. my God.
He actually released it.
He released it!
Fall back! Fall back!
Clock is ticking.
We have 36 hours.
or these passengers
are gonna die
of exposure to EMA.
We've gotta talk to Jaco
and figure out why he did this.
Unfortunately.
he is still unconscious.
Passengers nearly
tore him apart.
Look at this.
I feel like I'm back in Mosul.
Only in Midtown. right?
Do you think the National
Guard deployed a cell jammer?
Because my signal is shot.
- Yeah. No.
I saw Anna's team tearing up
all the surveillance.
Huh. she's doing everything
she can to keep the lid on this.
This is a cover-up.
We're with the CDC.
No one is in
any immediate danger.
But we need
to keep you quarantined
as a precaution
while we investigate.
You know what. partner?
I think you may be right.
Let us out!
You can't keep us in here.
Please. just cooperate.
It's in everyone's interest.
I've gotta call my wife!
What did he give us?
As soon as our
investigators determine
what you were exposed to.
we will keep you all informed.
This is insane.
She knows exactly
what they're exposed to.
She's lying.
Yeah. the less they know.
the better.
Let's see what we can
pull out of her.
Yeah.
Hey. buddy.
Everything's gonna be OK.
- I'm scared.
- I know you are.
But I need you
to be strong for me.
Can you do that?
Are we... are we gonna die?
We're gonna do
everything in our power
to make sure you
get out of there soon.
All right?
All right.
- What did you do to us?
- Yo!
- Hey. is he awake?
- What did you do to us?
No. no. no. no!
Don't hurt him!
Let him talk.
Bring him to the window.
Tell them what you told me.
Go on.
No one has to die.
My brothers are in possession
of a treatment to EMA.
It can be yours for a price.
- Oh. my God.
- There's a cure!
Hold on.
What's the price?
Release this man.
and the treatment is yours.
If you don't.
everyone on this bus will die.
Hey. so we just heard
from Kingsdale.
and they searched
Eloise Karcher's computer.
It turns out she was working on
a monoclonal antibody serum
on her own.
It's untested.
but it does exist.
Now. here's the bad news.
Let me guess... the terrorists
took it with the cooler.
Exactly.
and according to her boss.
it would take weeks.
if not months. to develop more.
Time we do not have.
So now Vyrestrat is using
this treatment as leverage.
What do we know about
the man they want released?
Right.
Well. here's the strange part.
Name's Lorik Basha.
But he's not South African.
He's an Albanian oligarch.
And that's not even
the weirdest part.
Interpol doesn't have the guy.
so we figured he must be
in our custody.
- Which he is not.
- No.
The JOC scoured
every database...
BOP. PACER. you name it.
We can't release him
because we don't have him.
That's not entirely true.
He's at a black site.
and you know exactly which one.
Lorik Basha financed
terror attacks all over Europe.
I admit that we didn't
connect him to Vyrestrat.
but it makes sense.
He shares their
abhorrent worldview.
Death to all
non-whites everywhere.
More or less.
How long have we had him?
Three years.
He was unofficially renditioned
from his home in Tirana
and taken to our secondary site
near the Indian Ocean.
far from any Article III
jurisdiction.
So we can't even confirm
we have him.
I wouldn't advise it.
Well. we're not gonna let
18 American civilians
die of hemorrhagic fever
in the middle of Manhattan.
Which means your team
needs to figure out
where Vyrestrat is holding
that serum and get it back.
All right. How we doing?
Is it possible Lorik Basha
is harboring these guys?
Does he have any property
in the city?
We've been looking.
So far. nothing.
OK. well. what about...
what about family. friends?
Everything dries up
after we vanished him.
All right. well.
there's gotta be a crumb. right?
Hey. Lorik Basha's name pops
up on a FinCEN investigation
four years ago.
Counterterror looked
into allegations
he laundered money through
failed real estate ventures.
Still owns the Majestic
Imperial Hotel in Queens.
That closed down years ago.
So it's abandoned.
Let's roll the dice.
Looks like our new friends
are loaded for bear.
All right. look.
What happened at Times Square.
it was a mess.
Who could have predicted
he'd take a bus hostage?
You were reckless.
So from now on. you're gonna
take orders from us.
The only way we walk out of here
is if we work together.
Anybody got
a problem with that?
What's the ROE?
You follow our lead.
Hotel's been abandoned
for years.
No idea how many guys
are dug in.
Keep eyes peeled for
an insulated medical bag.
EMA serum should be inside.
Cover!
Second floor. running.
You two. go with Scola and Eva.
We're gonna split up.
We'll take high. You take low.
Copy that. Come on.
- Move.
- Let's move.
Clear.
Nice shot.
Thanks.
Move!
Ooh. now we're playing!
Keep clearing this floor.
OA. with me.
Copy that.
Floor is secure.
but no sign of the serum.
Copy.
Clear the basement.
Copy that.
Maggie!
- He's down.
- Cover me.
Go. go. go. go. go!
He's dead.
Got it.
All right.
let's get out of here.
Jubal. we got the serum.
We're gonna head back now.
Jubal. Jubal.
Why aren't the comms working?
Hey.
Yeah. that's our fault.
- Whoa. whoa. whoa.
- Whoa. what are you doing?
Nice work.
We'll take that bag.
What the hell are you doing.
Devon?
We're on the same side.
Different bosses.
different games.
Our orders were clear.
Take possession
of the treatment.
I'm not giving it up.
OA. this one's
outside your jurisdiction.
Don't test me.
Just hand it over.
And what if I don't?
You're gonna shoot me?
Not you.
Maggie!
I told you not to test me.
Now hand over the treatment.
or my next shot
won't hit her vest.
There are people on that bus.
They are sick. scared.
and going to die.
We can help them together.
I won't ask again.
OK! OK!
You want it?
Just take it.
Take it.
Smart choice.
OA. on your six!
Shut up!
Had to pick the hard way.
Maggie!
Maggie.
Oh. my God.
Are you two OK?
Those guys had different
orders from the jump.
If we don't get
that serum back.
the people on the bus
are gonna die.
OK. look. Jubal called.
said that the DOD
moved the bus so they could
treat the passengers.
What do you mean.
they moved the bus?
Where?
Classified.
Why lock us out now?
What if they have
no intention
of treating those passengers?
I mean. this was all just one
big science experiment to them.
And Anna did it again.
She can't keep
getting away with this.
But she will.
Unless someone does
something about it.
Isobel. where's the bus?
All right. all right.
take a deep breath.
This has been a hard day for
everyone. and we are all on...
Where did they move the bus?
What bus?
We didn't come in here
to be gaslit.
There was no bus.
There was no exposure.
There was no containment.
Do you understand me?
Today never happened.
There were 18 Americans
on that bus.
People saw it.
The military was everywhere.
We cannot sweep this
under the rug
and pretend it never happened.
The official story
is the DSCA sent
Army Ordnance techs
to investigate
a possible IED on an MTA bus.
Your field report
will corroborate.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
At least tell us that
these people are being treated.
I can't.
I can't because I don't know.
This is above
all of our clearances.
They shot Maggie.
They assaulted me.
These people have to be
held accountable.
The man who shot Agent Bell
will be disciplined.
- And what about the rest?
- What about Anna Vorpe?
OK. you know what?
Keep your voices down.
You are both on the verge
of insubordination.
- Oh. is that right?
- Yes.
And you're already on thin ice
after your behavior
on surveillance
with Agent Ushruf.
She took the fall
for both of you.
You want some
professional advice?
Don't squander it.
You are a disgrace
to the bureau.
And you're fired.
- Hold on.
- Effective immediately.
OK.
Whoa. whoa.
Wait. wait.
What the hell just happened?
I'm out.
- What?
- He just got fired.
Green just fired him
on the spot.
There's got... there's gotta be
some kind of misunderstanding.
No. he's protecting them.
They broke the law.
and he's protecting them.
I'm sorry. sir.
It's been a pleasure.
Bro. come on.
No. no.
Come on.
- I know. I know.
No.
OA. this can't be happening.
It's OK.
OA...
You know how much
I've lost this year.
I...
I cannot lose you too.
You're never gonna
lose me. Mags.
Thank you.
You had quite the day.
I don't want to hear it.
Anna.
My father was in
the 37th engineer battalion.
deployed to Khamisiyah. Iraq.
in the '90s.
His squad was exposed to VX.
Ten times more lethal
than Sarin gas.
It's horrible.
There were no viable
treatment options back then.
so that exposure
cost my dad his life.
What I did today.
what my team did.
we did to protect
our future soldiers.
so that no one
would have to suffer
the way that my dad did.
You are a good storyteller.
I'll give you that.
What happens to the people
on the bus?
The hard truth?
There was only so much serum.
Priority one
is making sure that
we can replicate it at scale.
Those people will be dead
long before that.
But they won't die in vain.
We're studying the effects
of EMA exposure
for the greater good.
If you came down here
to clear your conscience.
I can't help you with that.
My strike team works
off the books for the DOD.
It just so happens
that we're down a man.
You'd be an asset. OA.
Think about it.
This round's on Uncle Sam.
Hey.
Anna made her move.
I'm in.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org